<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="traditional">
        <item>Indonesian Fried Rice (Nasi Goreng)</item>
        <item>Indonesian Satay</item>
        <item>Indonesian Oxtail Soup (Sop Buntut)</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="desc">
        <item>Nasi Goreng, Indonesian fried rice. This dish can be enjoyed by itself or as the basis of a larger meal, for example with a rijsttafel. It is very easy to make and won't take more than 20 minutes to prepare.</item>
        <item>This is an original Indonesian satay. I send it from a long way. Hope all over the world, readers can enjoy it.</item>
        <item>This is my version of Indonesian Sop Buntot, which is a deeply comforting oxtail and vegetable soup. Rich in collagen and filled with complex flavors, I always serve this with steamed rice and extra sliced tomatoes, fish sauce, shallot flakes (or French-fried onions), and lime wedges on the side.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ingredients1">
    <item>
        One cup uncooked white rice
	</item>
	<item>
        Three tablespoons soy sauce
    </item>
    <item>
        Four shallots, peeled and halved
    </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ingredients2">
        <item>
            Two cups water
		</item>
		<item>
            Three tablespoons tomato sauce
		</item>
        <item>
            One large onion, quartered, divided
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ingredients3">
        <item>
            Cooking spray
		</item>
		<item>
            One tablespoons peanut oil
		</item>
        <item>
            One (two inches) piece ginger, peeled and thinly sliced across the grain
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ingredients4">
        <item>
            Three eggs, beaten
		</item>
		<item>
            Two cloves garlic, peeled and minced
		</item>
        <item>
            Five cloves garlic, peeled
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ingredients5">
        <item>
            One tablespoon vegetable oil
		</item>
		<item>
            One pinch ground black pepper
		</item>
        <item>
            Three tablespoons canola oil
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ingredients6">
        <item>
            One onion, chopped
		</item>
		<item>
            One pinch ground cumin
		</item>
        <item>
            Six whole cloves (optional)
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ingredients7">
        <item>
            One leek, chopped
		</item>
		<item>
            Six skinless, boneless hicken breast halves - cubed
		</item>
        <item>
            A half teaspoon ground nutmeg
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ingredients8">
        <item>
            One clove garlic, minced
		</item>
		<item>
            One tablespoon vegetable oil
		</item>
        <item>
            A quarter teaspoon ground cinnamon
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ingredients9">
        <item>
            Two green chile peppers, chopped
        </item>
        <item>
            A quarter up minced onion
        </item>
        <item>
            Four pounds meaty oxtail pieces, at room temperature
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ingredients10">
        <item>
            A half pound skinless, boneless chicken breasts, cut into thin strips
        </item>
        <item>
            One cclove garlic, peeled and minced
        </item>
        <item>
            Two large carrots, cut into two inches pieces
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ingredients11">
    <item>
        A half pound peeled and deveined prawns
	</item>
	<item>
        One cup water
    </item>
    <item>
        Three stalks celery, cut into one inch pieces
    </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ingredients12">
        <item>
            One teaspoon ground coriander
		</item>
		<item>
            A half cup chunky peanut butter
		</item>
        <item>
            Water to cover
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ingredients13">
        <item>
            One teaspoon ground cumin
		</item>
		<item>
            Two tablespoons soy sauce
		</item>
        <item>
            Two teaspoons salt
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ingredients14">
        <item>
            Three tablespoons sweet soy sauce (Indonesian kecap manis)
		</item>
		<item>
            Two tablespoons white sugar
		</item>
        <item>
            A half teaspoon ground black pepper
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ingredients15">
        <item></item>
		<item>
            One tablespoon lemon juice
		</item>
        <item>
            Three waxy potatoes, scrubbed and cut into one and a half inches chunks
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ingredients16">
        <item></item>
		<item>
            Skewers
		</item>
        <item>
            Three large carrots, cut into two inchec pieces
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ingredients17">
        <item></item>
		<item></item>
        <item>
            Two tablespoons white sugar
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ingredients18">
        <item></item>
		<item></item>
        <item>
            Two tablespoons fish sauce
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ingredients19">
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item>
            Three ripe roma tomatoes, sliced horizontally into a half inch wedges
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ingredients20">
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item>
            One (two point eight ounce) can French fried onions
        </item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="step1">
        <item>
            Bring the rice and water to a boil in a saucepan over high heat. Reduce heat to medium-low, cover, and simmer until the rice is tender, and the liquid has been absorbed, 20 to 25 minutes.
            Spread onto a baking sheet, and refrigerate 2 hours until cold.
		</item>
        <item>
            In a bowl, mix soy sauce, tomato sauce, peanut oil, garlic, black pepper, and cumin. Place chicken into the mixture, and stir to coat.
            Cover, and marinate in the refrigerator for at least 15 minutes, but not overnight. This will make the meat too dark.
        </item>
        <item>
            Combine shallots, 2 onion quarters, ginger, and garlic in a food processor; pulse into a paste.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="step2">
        <item>
            Heat a large nonstick skillet over medium heat. Spray with nonstick cooking spray. Pour eggs into hot skillet. Cook until the eggs begin to set,
            lifting up the edges of the set eggs to allow the uncooked egg to contact the hot pan, about 1 minute. Flip omelet in one piece and cook until fully set,
            about 30 seconds. Slice omelet into 1/2 inch strips.
		</item>
		<item>
            Preheat the grill for high heat.
		</item>
        <item>
            Heat oil in a large pot over medium-high heat; cook and stir cloves, nutmeg, and cinnamon until fragrant, about 30 seconds.
            Add shallot paste and fry until fragrant and slightly browned, 2 to 3 minutes. Add oxtails; stir until completely covered with spices and paste and browned, about 5 minutes.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="step3">
        <item>
            Heat the vegetable oil in a wok or large frying pan over high heat. Stir in the onion, leek, garlic, and chile peppers.
            Cook, stirring, until onion is soft, 3 to 5 minutes. Stir in the chicken, prawns, coriander, and cumin, mixing well. Cook and stir for approximately 5 minutes.
		</item>
		<item>
            Heat vegetable oil in a saucepan over medium heat, and saute onion and garlic until lightly browned. Mix in water, peanut butter, soy sauce, and sugar.
            Cook and stir until well blended. Remove from heat, mix in lemon juice, and set aside.
		</item>
        <item>
            Stir remaining onion quarters, 2 carrots, and celery into the pot. Pour in enough water to cover by 2 inches. Bring to a boil; reduce heat, cover, and simmer until oxtail is tender, about 5 hours.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="step4">
        <item>
            Mix in the cold rice, sweet soy sauce, and omelet strips;
            cook until shrimp are bright pink and chicken is no longer pink in the center, 3 to 5 minutes.
        </item>
        <item>
            Lightly oil the grill grate. Thread chicken onto skewers, and discard marinade.
            Grill skewers about 5 minutes per side, until chicken juices run clear. Serve with the peanut sauce.
        </item>
        <item>
            Stir salt, black pepper, potatoes, and 3 carrots into the pot.
            Increase heat and simmer soup until potatoes and carrots are tender, about 15 minutes. Add sugar and fish sauce; stir well to combine.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="step5">
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item>
            Ladle soup into large serving bowls and top with tomato wedges and French-fried onions.
        </item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="pict">
        <item>@drawable/friedrice</item>
        <item>@drawable/satay</item>
        <item>@drawable/sopbuntut</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
